important to see mistakes
as part of learning?
I think it's because
mistakes are not signs
of failure, but signs
of effort and growth.
Seeing them this way
helps people stay motivated
and keep trying.
Cool answer, Gwen. Thank
you. Now it's my
turn. How does being
kind to yourself change
motivation? Well, I guess
it helps reduce anxiety
and self-blame. This creates
a healthier mindset that
supports long-term effort even
when things are difficult.
That's right. Our dear
friends, what do you
think? Don't forget to
share your answers in
the comments below. It's
not about right or
wrong. What matters is
growing and understanding together. What